Adise Mamoye

Full Stack Developer

Jacksonville, Florida | 516-838-9131 | adisemamo211@gmail.com <u>Github | LinkedIn | Portfolio | Recommendation Letter</u>

PERSONAL SUMMARY

I am a software developer with a passion for creating beautiful, functional, and user-friendly web applications. I specialize in frontend development with Vue.js, but I'm also experienced with the entire web stack and enjoy working on full-stack projects. When I'm not coding, you'll find me exploring new technologies, with a desire to learn, develop and improve every day.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Frontend: Vue.js, React.js, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Material-UI, Vuetify

Backend: Node.js, Express.js

Database: PostgreSQL, Firestore (Firebase) **Version Control:** Git, GitHub, SourceTree

Tools: Redux, Prisma, Firebase Auth, Firebase Hosting, Azure DevOps, CI CD

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Hadera, North, Israel 01/2023 - Present

Wyze - Cloud Knowledge Management System

- Lead the frontend development of a cloud-based knowledge management system
- Reduced support team response time by 42%, improving overall customer satisfaction.
- Implemented CI/CD pipeline that decreased deployment time by 70%
- Led the migration from Vue 2 to Vue 3 for the major project.
- Skills: Vue.js, Pinia, Vuetify, Azure DevOps, JavaScript, Git, SourceTree.

Full Stack Developer

Austin,TX, USA

Moyae - Electronic Health Record System

07/2022 - 01/2023

- Optimized treatment time for ophthalmologists and optometrists by developing a comprehensive Electronic Health Record (EHR) system that improved operational efficiency.
- Played a key role in developing scalable, maintainable code for various system features
- Integrated advanced frontend technologies to provide a modern user interface
- Supported long-term application growth and reliability.
- Skills: React.js, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL, JavaScript, Vuex, Prisma, RESTful APIs

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

SalesPro - Github | Website

A serverless CRM platform aimed at helping businesses manage customer data and sales. Inspired by Salesforce, the app is built with Vue 3 and utilizes Vuetify for UI components and Firebase for authentication, database and hosting. Technologies used: Vue 3, Vuetify, Firestore, Firebase Auth, Firebase Hosting, Azure DevOps (for CI/CD), Git, Github.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, JavaScript program

Ramat-Gan, Israel

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

Intensive JavaScript program with a focus on full-stack web development.

03/2022 - 06/2022

LANGUAGES

English: Fluent Hebrew: Native Amharic: Advanced